https://github.com/anitalh

#### **SUMMARY**

I am a result driven technology professional with 4 years of software engineering industry experience. I am currently a grad student at Northeastern University, Seattle pursuing a master's in Information Systems. My core areas of interest include cloud services, web development, data Analytics and project management.

# **EDUCATION**

### M.S in Information Systems

## Northeastern University-Seattle

Sep 2022 - May 2024

• Coursework: Application Engineering and Development, Web Design and User Experience Engineering, Network Structures and cloud computing, Program Structures and Algorithms

## **B.E in Electrical Engineering**

#### **BMSIT Bangalore**

Aug 2012 - June 2016

• Coursework: C programming, Micro controllers

#### **SKILLS**

- Languages: Java, Python, C#, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, XML
- FrontEnd frameworks: ReactJs, Mocha chai
- BackEnd Frameworks: Java Spring MVC, Java Spring Boot, Selenium
- Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Redis, AWS Redshift (Familiar)
- Tools & Technologies: Docker, Zookeeper, Kafka, Junit, Nunit, Git, Gradle, Maven, Jenkins, Eclipse, BugZilla, Jira, TFS, kibana, APIGEE, SOAPUI, Postman, Seetest, OAuth, Rest APIs, Json

### **EMPLOYMENT**

### **Senior Systems Engineer**

Infosys Ltd

Nov 2019 - July 2022

Technology stack: C#, Selenium, Seetest, OAuth, NUnit.

- Implemented selenium automation test framework for a US healthcare major 'Medtronic' in c# and selenium for OAuth2 based Identity Access Management.
- Redesigned and Implemented automation framework for few features of patient monitoring system and enhancement of existing scripts. Testing the patient monitoring system to checkthe functionality.
- Reporting, tracking, and retesting the bugs in the software via TFS. Conducting a triage meeting to deliver the software within the sprint ensuring the quality.

# **Software Engineer in Test**

**Torry Harris Business Solutions** 

June 2017 - Oct 2019

Technology stack: JavaScript, Cucumber, HTTP Protocol, OAuth2, Kibana, Java, Selenium, TestNG.

- Worked on creating automation scripts and performed integration testing, regression testing of complex rest APIs related to add on packages, data rollover for a UK Telecom major EE.
- worked on enhancing the automation scripts and integration testing of several Rest APIs such as location tracker, network tracker for British Telecom, valid customer verification and password reset for user accounts for a television network NOW TV, and payment through a third-party site for an e-commerce major Amazon in On-Prem environment.

# **Projects**

Dynamic and Real-Time Personalized Recommendation based on Social Network Analysis

Tech-Stack: Python WSGI, Kafka

A recommendation System built using sentimental analysis and user implicit feedback technique provides a dynamic real-time recommendation that is more appropriate for the user's current behavior.

- Task Management App | HTML, CSS, React, Java Spring Boot, OAuth
  - A Web app capable of adding to-do tasks, updating the tasks, and deleting tasks for a unique user.
- Train Scheduler | Python WSGI
  - Simple Python-based Web Service which provides a list of earliest trains from a given source to destination
- Inventory Management System | Tech-Stack: Java, Swing, JDBC and MySQL
  - A system helps to track the inventory, customers and user details for physical retail stores.
- Fitz Freak | Tech-Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React
  - An e-commerce application that displays gym products and its types instore and demo/contact form